视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
翻译：bunny jophy cici rubens
校对：佳佳 肉丝 小p 水 小南
铁杉树丛
第二季  第一集
总监：darren 慕斯
时轴：络睿    后期：hhjie
他去哪了
Where did he go?
谢谢 Papa Joe
Thank you, Papa Joe.
一路顺风
Travel safe.
猜猜是谁
Guess who?
嘿 我太想你了 coz
Hmm, man! I've missed you, coz.
我还以为你会来不了了
I didn't think you were gonna make it.
在阿尔图纳时我没油了
I ran out of gas in Altoona.
我被跟踪到扬斯敦郊外
I got followed into a ladies'
一间货柜停车场的女厕
room at a truck stop outside of Youngstown.
我不得不认真的干一架
I had to give a serious ass-kicking.
现在我来了
But I am here now.
天啊
Oh, man!
我小的时候Joe常常把我抱在膝上
Joe used to bounce me on his knee when I was little,
尽管那时候他已经很老 皱纹很多
and he was old as the hills and twice as wrinkly, even then.
你过得怎样
How's your life?
依然活着
I show up every day.
你造你们走后日子有点寂寞
It's lonely with you guys gone, you know?
我跟妈妈在几周内搬到了西部 西雅图
Mom and I are headed out West in a couple of weeks. Seattle.
你怎么不一起来
Why don't you come with?
咖啡因和毛毛细雨
Caffeine and drizzle?
铁杉树丛给你留下了什么
What's left for you in Hemlock Grove?
也许有吧 让我想想
Maybe. Let me think about it.
伙计 你看看这些老头
Man, would you look at all these old farts?
- 那是谁 -我不造
- Who is that guy? - I have no clue.
他看起来像得到了精神战利品
Looks like he's got booty on his mind.
恩 在葬礼上
Ew! At a funeral?
看在上帝的份上 尊重一下死者吧
Have some respect for the dead, for Christ's sake.
-嘿    -嗨
- Hey... - Hi!
嘿
Hey!
嗨
Hi.
你得来见见 Sonya阿姨   要一起来吗
You have to come meet Aunt Sonya. You wanna come?
好 我开了200英里都没有尿尿 但我会赶上 好吗
OK, I haven't peed in 200 miles, but I'll catch up. OK?
好的 来 他来了
All right, come. Here he is!
- -
好看么 变态
Get a good look, you sick bastard?
你完全不记得我了 是不
You don't remember me at all, do you?
我们两家在UP共用一个营地
Our families shared a campsite in the UP
当爸爸们去砍树
when our dads got work cutting trees.
96年的夏天
Summer of '96.
我常常看着你这小溪中游泳
I used to watch you swimming in the creek.
-真可怕 我那时才九岁 -
- That's creepy. I was nine. -
我只是保护着你们的安全
I was just looking out for the safety of all you kids.
Andreas Vasilescu
Andreas Vasilescu.
我开着梦幻雪糕车
I used to drive the Dairy Dream truck.
我给所有罗马小孩免费雪糕
I gave free ice cream to all the Roma kids.
-是你           - 香橙奶油雪糕
- That was you? - Orange Creamsicle.
- 依旧被吸引着    -
- Still addicted. -
那个夏天我Tobar叔叔从一棵蓝云杉上掉了下来
My Uncle Tobar fell out of a blue spruce that summer
落在他的电锯上
and landed on his chainsaw.
我记得他们带走了每一块碎片
I remember them taking the pieces away.
小女孩长成了大美女
To little girls who grow up to be beautiful women.
巧言善辩的男人
To silver-tongued men
带着甜蜜危险的笑容
with sweet, dangerous smiles.
好 好 再见
- - Yes, yes! Bye.
- 那是什么             - 她有一个适合你的女孩
- What was that about? - She has a girl for you
可以给你擦地板忍受你众多孩子的女孩
who will scrub your floors and bear you many children.
什么样子的
What girl?
挺美的
Pretty.
擦地板只是小事 等等
Clean floors are nothing to sneeze on. At.
你是个好父亲
You would have been a good father.
好丈夫    我知道现在看起来是不可能
A good husband. I know it seems impossible now,
但其他人会克服
but someone else will come along.
都过去了
Letha's gone.
让她走吧
Let her go.
让我们去吃点儿什么吧
Let's get something to eat.
恩
Hmm!
曾经 Joe那般地位的人的葬礼
Used to be, the burial of a man of Joe's stature
会有上千个罗马人参加
would have brought a thousand Romani.
如今有多少人
Today, how many?
一百个
A hundred?
现在所有的孩子都只想着向前
All you kids want to do nowadays is move on,
想变成真正的美国人
become real Americans.
真伤心
It breaks my heart.
时代不同了
Well, times are changing.
现在世界也不一样了
The world's different now.
世界总是在变化
The world's always changing.
不表示日子越来越好了
Doesn't mean it's getting better.
不要忘记你是谁 你们的身份
Don't forget who you are or who your people are.
你妈妈怎么样了
How is your mother anyway?
告诉他我总是想起她
Tell her I'm always thinking of her,
担心她是否会寂寞
wondering if she's lonely.
别动
Freeze!
不要跑
Do not run!
不要试图抵抗或拒捕
Do not attempt to resist arrest.
我们有搜查令的
We have a warrant to search the premises.
Lynda
Lynda!
把手放在能看见的地方
Keep your hands in plain sight!
Lynda
Lynda!
我们有某个人的逮捕令
We have warrants for the arrest of specific individuals.
- 停止挣扎        -  放开我
- Stop struggling. - Ow! Get off of me!
- 你他妈的在干什么        - 停止抵抗
- The fuck are you doing? - Stop resisting!
- Peter  - 过来
- Peter! - Come here!
他们抓了Lynda
They got Lynda.
我的车停在房子后面
My Harley's parked behind the house.
信用卡诈骗  空白支票诈骗
"Credit card fraud, check kiting,
制造假冒障碍标识语
manufacturing counterfeit handicap placards,
挂美国农业部合格牛绞肉的名字卖老鼠肉
selling muskrat meat as USDA certified ground beef,
扮成小丑潜入马戏团
trespassing as a circus clown."
她打算对那头幼象做什么
What was she planning to do with the baby elephant?
她认识了一个男人
She knew a guy.
你母亲日子过得很精彩
Your mother's led a colorful life.
都是废话 她被拒绝保释
It's total bullshit that her bail was denied.
Lynda没有威胁到任何一个人
Lynda's not a threat to anybody.
法律的实施是以防万一罗马人
Law enforcement is making a case that the Romani
是一个有组织的犯罪集团
are an organized criminal enterprise.
相信我 他母亲不是有组织的
His mother's not organized, trust me.
这些指控都是无足轻重的
These charges are small-time.
- 他们只是米老鼠        - 不要紧
- They're Mickey Mouse. - Doesn't matter.
根据联邦反诈骗腐败组织集团犯罪法 他们正在调查她
They're coming after her under federal RICO statutes.
诈骗
Racketeering.
这就是政府
It's how the government
如何传送保证美国安全的信息
sends the message it's keeping America safe.
你母亲会面临一段艰难的时期
Your mother could be facing serious time.
-  多久     - 得看涉及的有多少
- How much? - Depends on how much of this
检察官正试着起诉
the prosecution tries to make stick.
她会被引渡回铁杉郡面对指控
She's being extradited back to Hemlock County to face charges.
你可以跟我住在一起
You can stay with me.
至少 她会有家人陪在身边
At least, she'll have family close by.
她将会回到铁衫郡这是好的 对吗
It's good that she'll be back in Hemlock Grove, right?
不一定 那法官是个娘们 但我认识检察官
Mixed. The judge is a twat, but I know the prosecutor.
- 我们可以试试辩护           - 她不能服役
- We could try to plea down. - She can't do a stretch.
她不是黑人也不是西班牙人    雅利安人
She's not Black or Hispanic, and the Aryan slime
只想着结束希特勒对我们做过的事
just want to finish off what Hitler did to our people.
没有人暗地里守护着她
She has no one looking out for her on the inside.
我的预付金是20,000
My retainer's 20,000.
恩
Um...
不能分期付款吗
Can that be paid in installments?
预先支付 所以才叫预付金
Up-front. That's what "Retainer" Means.
我没有2万美金
I don't have $20,000.
20美金都没有 什么也没有
I don't have $20. I don't have shit.
恩
Well...
我私藏了差不多500美金
I've got about $500 stashed
还有一串珠宝 我们可以在eBay上卖了
and a bunch of junk jewelry we can sell on eBay.
- 所以 我们算是坑了  - 基本上是的
- So basically, we're fucked. - Basically.
你不像是在铁衫树丛没有朋友的人
It's not like you don't have friends in Hemlock Grove.
没有
No.
也许这是一个机会
Maybe this is an opportunity.
一个改善关系的时机
A time to mend fences.
Peter
Peter?
- Peter  - 什么 怎么了
- Peter? - What? What?
我们会解决的 小表弟
We're gonna figure this out, cousin.
Lynda会没事的
Lynda's gonna be fine.
Godfrey公司增强了
Godfrey Industries has increased its profitability
最后17处地方的盈利性 在生物技术
for the last 17 quarters, leading the field in biotech,
药物 基因工程等领域居领先地位
pharmaceuticals, and genetic engineering.
我很高兴地宣布 我们已经连续四年
I am pleased to report we are, for the fourth year in a row,
在北美私营企业中
the largest privately held
栖居榜首
corporation of its kind in North America.
我有两个想法
Couple of thoughts.
有人去过毛伊岛吗
Anybody been to Maui?
没人吗
No one?
我刚从那里回来
I just got back.
那里比他们说的还要美
It's even more beautiful than they say.
和Healani Kaulakakui打个招呼
- - Say hello to Healani Kaulakakui.
Roman 我看不出这有什么关系
Roman, I don't see how this is relevant.
我上了这姑娘
I fucked this girl.
上了她很多次
I fucked her a lot.
我能在这说这些吗
Can I say that here?
你想说什么就说什么
You can say what you want...
Godfrey是行业领袖
Godfrey Industries is a leader
在3D器官打印领域 是吗
in three-dimensional organ printing, right?
由它首创的 我们在做再生胆囊功能的
Pioneered it. We're in clinical trials on the beta version
测试样本的临床测试
for regenerating gallbladder function.
但那项技术的目标人群快死了
But the target demographic for that technology will be dead soon,
给我们的回头客造成损失
which puts a big dent in repeat business.
我们应关注我们的基因工程
We should be focusing our genetic engineering
去加强年轻人的体验
on enhancing the youth experience.
更大 更好 更紧 更长 更厚
Bigger, better, tighter, longer, thicker...
我向你保证 Healani Kaulakakui只想派对没日没夜地进行下去
I guarantee you, Healani Kaulakakui never wants the party to end.
或许我们待会在补充报道中再讨论这个问题
Perhaps we can discuss this later during sidebar.
先生们 感谢聆听
Gentlemen, thank you for your time.
快速提问
Quick question...
关于季度盈利报告
about the quarterly earnings report.
第47个表格的 杂项 R 和 D 是什么回事
Table 47. Miscellaneous R and D. What's that?
R和D 那是杂项
R and D that's miscellaneous.
看起来在杂项上花费了很多位数
Seems like a lot of zeroes are being spent on miscellaneous.
-用做什么 -完全是技术上的
- What for? - It's extremely technical.
看来你需要进修一个古病毒学更高级的学位
You'd need an advanced degree in paleovirology
才能开始理解
to even begin to understand.
你们当中有人进修古孤病毒学吗
Any of you guys got an advanced degree in paleovirology?
所以 我数百万的钱
So, millions of dollars of my money...
都被花在没人知道是什么的东西上
is being spent, and no one knows on what.
现在 这感觉不太对头
Now, that just doesn't feel right.
我母亲走了
My mother's gone.
从现在起 你们要对付的是我
From now on, you'll be dealing with me.
这堆搪塞的废话不会飞
And this runaround bullshit isn't gonna fly.
懂我的意思吗
You feel me on that?
Roman 你是一个聪明的年轻人
Roman, you're a bright young man.
一起合作 就没有我们做不到的事
Together, there's no limit to what we can...
把这些话留到你的办公室再说 好吗
Let's take this to your office, shall we?
我一直都很理解你的家庭
I've always had an understanding with your family.
我保持Godfrey产业的盈利
I keep Godfrey Industries profitable,
在我觉得合适的事情上我有自由的空间去发挥
I'm given a free hand to run things as I see fit.
--你瞒报了多少
- - How much are you skimming?
你不知道你自己在说什么
You have absolutely no idea what you're talking about.
这是没有道理的 不公平的 错误的
That was uncalled for, unfair, and wrong.
我在这里问了个问题 我期望得到一个回答
I asked a question in there. I expect an answer.
除非我得到答案 我会冻结所有进一步的基金
Until I get one, I'm putting a freeze on all further funding.
你没有那个权利
- You don't have the authority. - My mother and Norman
我妈妈和Norman不在乎你的目的是什么
didn't give a shit about
但你的欢快日子到头了
whatever it is you're up to, but the joyride's over.
每个人都有
Everyone has secrets locked
藏在门背后的秘密 Roman
away behind closed doors somewhere, Roman.
我知道你会想我守住你的
I'm certain you'd like me to keep yours.
你不会想和我搅合的 Pryce
Oh, you don't want to squab with me, Pryce.
最终的结果对你不好
It won't come out well for you.
早上好 Olivia
Good morning, Olivia.
早上好 Pryce博士
"Good morning, Dr. Pryce.
我感觉像个大款
I feel like a million bucks!
这种感觉日渐强烈
I'm feeling stronger every day."
那是三个月前
It was three months ago.
现在是第十四周 看看我们的进展怎样了
It's week 14. Let's see how we're doing.
我感觉这休养没完没了
I'm feeling as if this recuperation is never gonna end.
多亏你 我感觉我讲话就像个剥玉米工
Thanks to you, I'm talking like I shuck corn for a living.
把怎么说话整个重新学习一遍需要时间
Learning how to speak all over again takes time.
耐心 我懂 我知道
Patience, I know, I know. Just spare me
只是当你提醒我是临床死亡 昏迷了两个月时
your daily "Ode to self" Where you remind me
放过我这种每天的 自我歌颂
I was clinically dead, in a coma for two months.
你打算把我当你的花边人质
How much longer do you intend to hold me as your gimp hostage?
张大嘴
Open wide.
你心情不太好
You're in a grim mood.
该死的 我很好
Damn, I'm good.
我们需要谈谈 Roman
We need to talk about Roman.
为什么 他向你问起我吗
Why? Did he ask about me?
也不算是
Not exactly.
让我们看看你的舌头灵活度
Let's check your lingual dexterity.
上
Up...
下
down...
左 右
left, right.
Johann 告诉我
Johann, talk to me.
让我们看看你的腿
Let's have a look at your leg.
噢 还有明显的肌肉萎缩
Oh, there's still significant muscle atrophy.
有1.5英寸的差别
An inch and a half difference.
缩短收肌得到供体组织的舌移植后
To be expected after shortening the adductor magnus
这种情况也在意料之中
to harvest the donor tissue for the lingual transplant...
Johann 该死的
Johann, damn it!
你儿子像是宇宙的主人
Your son's been playing master of the universe.
到处给下马威 窥探书本资料
He's throwing his weight around, snooping through the books.
他威胁如果我不解释我们的一些敏感支出
He threatened to terminate me if I don't explain some of our...
就要了结我
more sensitive expenditures.
他不了解你的工作对我们家庭多重要
He has no idea how critical your work is to our family.
对他也是
To him.
真讽刺
Ironic.
他现在应该开始饥渴了吧
He must be starting to get hungry by now.
是的
Yes.
我不知道他怎么才满足
I wonder how he's been satiating.
我不敢想象
I shudder to think.
你永远不能满足于我 不是吗
You just can't get enough of me, can you?
先付钱 再开始
First you pay, then we play.
都在这里了
It's all there.
你想我养新的吗
You want me to start a new crop?
今晚开始
Start tonight.
-这需要一些时间 -下次两倍价钱
- It'll take a few days. - Twice as many next time.
做得好
Nice digs.
听我说 我知道我们分开后事情都很糟糕
Look, I know things were bad when I split...
-滚你的 -听我说
- Fuck you. - Just hear me out.
-没兴趣 我们之间结束了 -拜托
- Not interested. We're done. - Please.
Lynda进了监狱 我需要你的帮忙
Lynda's in jail. I need your help.
不
No.
擦 你可以对我很差 但我们现在讲的是Lynda
Fuck. Be mad at me. But this is Lynda we're talking about.
听起来她搞砸了 不是我的问题
Sounds like she fucked up. Not my problem.
她一直对你很好 她在那里呆不下的
She was always good to you. She's not gonna make it in there.
你想我做什么
What do you want me to do about it?
我需要钱
I need money...
去请一个律师
to hire a lawyer.
所以你来这里乞讨
So you came here to beg.
你能借我两万块吗 我会还给你
Can you please loan me $20,000? I'll pay you back.
我一直很喜欢你妈妈
I always liked your mother.
她会拷曲奇
She baked cookies.
我妈妈从来没烤过曲奇
My mother never baked cookies.
我可以扔你一些面团
I can shoot you the dough.
我不会那样做 我不想理你
I'm not gonna do that. I'm not giving you shit.
也许你忘了我救过一命
Maybe you forgot I saved your life.
Shelley也救了你的
Shelley saved yours.
我一直想着她
I think about her all the time.
-她可能在外面某个地方 -她孤独地死去了
- She might still be out there. - She died alone.
当Letha死的时候 我需要你
And when Letha died, and I needed you,
你拍拍屁股就逃走了
you tucked your dick between your legs and ran away
像个小婊子一样
like the little fucking bitch you are.
滚出我家
Get out of my house.
Poman 拜托了
Roman, please...
滚出我的家
Get out of my house.
今天 我和Letha和她的宝宝说再见
Today, I said goodbye to Letha and her baby.
那个我再也抱不到的宝宝
The baby I never got to hold.
这段日子过得很糟糕
It's been hard these weeks,
要接受她们已经走了的事实
to accept the fact that they're both gone.
但将他们的骨灰撒在阿勒格尼
But spreading their ashes over the Allegheny
也给我带来些慰藉和安心
brought closure and resolution.
也许这也就是我和你告别的方式吧
Maybe this is my way of saying goodbye to you, too.
你就像我的女儿一样 Shelley
You were like a daughter to me, Shelley.
我希望我相信天堂的存在
I wish I believed in heaven.
那样我就有希望见到我的两个宝贝女孩
Then I'd have hope of seeing both my girls again.
一直爱着你们 Norman叔叔
Love always, Uncle Norman.
哦 天哪
Oh, Christ.
每年这个时候从厄尔瓜多进口
Imported from Ecuador this time of year.
我的碳足迹就这么多
So much for my carbon footprint.
Norman 你真贴心
Norman, it's so sweet of you.
额 我知道你要过来吗
Did I, uh, know you were coming over?
不 不 我 我只是想给你个惊喜
No. No, I... I wanted to, um, to surprise you.
你知道我讨厌惊喜 我的生活一团糟
You know I hate surprises. I'm a mess.
你知道我讨厌惊喜 我现在脑子里很乱
你要让自己放松下来 毕竟你刚从鬼门关走了一遭
You want to give yourself a break. Been to hell and back.
我想让你见见这个医生
There's this doctor that I want you to see.
他是 呃 他在治疗癫痫方面是个专家
He's... he's an expert in seizures.
一切尽在Johann的掌握中
Johann has everything under control.
我们太相信Pryce了
You put too much faith in Pryce.
我已经发过一次病了 那种感觉真是差到极点
I already bit my tongue off once. It was extremely unpleasant.
我可不想在犯一次癫痫
I have no intention of having another seizure
更不想再重复那种经历
and repeating the experience.
你知道么 我 我觉得我们可以出去走走 散散心
You know, I... I thought that we could get you out for a walk.
我不想让大家看到我拄着拐杖的样子
I do not want people staring
好像我是什么该死的残废一样
at me leaning on a cane like some damn invalid.
我可以开我的新车带你去兜兜风
I could bring my new car around and take you for a ride.
让你的头发也吹吹风
Get some wind in your hair.
你知道的 叶子都慢慢变黄了 它们
You know, the leaves are turning, it's...
-来嘛 -Pryce会抓狂的
- Come on! - Pryce will pitch a fit.
好吧 我们去吧
All right, let's do it.
这样才对嘛
Good girl.
Olivia 我对上帝发誓
Honest to God, Olivia,
你现在还像我哥把你带回家那天一样漂亮
you're as beautiful as the day my brother brought you home.
你为什么还留在这 Norman
What keeps you hanging around, Norman?
你为什么不带着你的钱 给自己买架飞机
Why not take your millions, buy yourself a jet,
找个年轻女郎去异国他乡逍遥快活
go somewhere... exotic with a 25-year-old?
我对生活所有的向往现在就站在我面前
Everything I want in life is standing right in front of me.
你就是我的全部
You're all I have left.
真的吗
Am I?
那你的侄子呢
What about your nephew?
他最近见你了吗
Has he been to see you?
他在忙一些 别的事
He's... busy with other matters.
谢谢你的花
Thanks for the flowers.
嗨 你来啦
Hey, you!
好吧 再怎么说我们也尝试了
Well, it was worth a try.
他就是一根该死的刺
He's a fucking prick.
你想吃点什么吗
You want something to eat?
不了 我不饿
No, I'm not hungry.
我能再借下你的车吗
Can I borrow the car again?
拜托了
Please.
就停在街上呢
It's on the street.
-谢了 -嗯
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm.
Peter
Peter!
别惹麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
你就是那个人 对吧
You're the guy, right?
谁在监视着你
Who's watching over you?
Saint Sebastian
Saint Sebastian.
我们赶紧把这操蛋活干完吧
Let's get this motherfucker done.
让我先看一眼酬劳
I wanna see the money first.
当我干完活的时候 钱还会是这么多 没错吧
It's all gonna be there when I count it, right?
他本就曾经贪污 现在自然多疑
"He that is already corrupt is naturally suspicious."
到底干不干
So are we gonna do this thing or what?
当然干
Yeah.
跟着我
Follow me.
你是第一个这么干的人
You're the first gadji to sample what my people
我的人觉得你是Saint Sebastian's Arrow的走狗
once referred to as "Saint Sebastian's Arrow."
恩 我听说了
Yeah, I heard of that.
干完这票你以后活的会很舒服的 我的朋友 可没那么多人能得到
Then you've lived a large life, my friend, not many people have.
什么是Gadji
What the fuck is a "Gadji"?
那是吉普赛人叫外来者的说法
It's what Gypsies call outsiders.
我已经抛弃了老观念
I'm dropping ancient knowledge here,
以前我只和自己人分享 现在我可以给你
shared only by my people, but now, I'm sharing it with you.
完全把那些老思想打倒了
Totally down with ancient knowledge.
就像金字塔一样 那又是什么
Like the pyramids... What was that shit about?
吉普赛人 小子
Gypsies, man.
吉普赛人 埃及人
Gypsies... Egyptians.
是我们 我们建了那些
That was us. We built that shit.
我觉得我就像是个听历史课的学生
And to think I consider myself a student of history.
我们在时间的迷雾里迷失了方向 而那个箭头所指的方向
The way of the arrow, like the true purposes of the pyramids,
就是金字塔的真正目的
was lost in the mists of time.
但是我把它带回来了
But I brought it back,
找到了改进的方法
figuring out a way to refine it.
做了一万多次尝试
Making it 10,000 times more potent.
-听起来挺傻的 -但来之不易 肯定没问题
- Sounds dope. - Comes on hard, you peak,
然后你就可以轻松的安定下来
then you settle down fast and easy.
就像是一只穿梭在时空里的箭
Like an arrow flying through time and space.
主要投资在于那二十个大的
Twenty large is a major investment.
-我们老大本来挺犹豫的 -但是你的老板
- Our boss was hesitant at first. - But your weed man...
-我们的客户 -为你担保
- Our client. - ... vouched for you,
所以我们才有了这次机会
so we're taking a shot.
你一定不会后悔
You will not regret this.
这甚至都不是毒品 真的 更像是
This isn't even a drug, really. It's more like a...
通向另一个空间的生物形态大门
a biomorphic portal into another dimension.
看起来能爽很久
Long as it fucks you up.
还给了我们老板一笔丰厚的利润
And gives our boss a profit on his capital.
先生们
Gentlemen...
我现在把Sebzilla给你们
I give you Sebzilla.
把头扬起来
Tilt your heads back.
哦 烧死我了
Ow! Shit burns!
好了
Good.
我没什么感觉
Yo, I don't feel anything.
最好不要耍我们 holmes
Better not be playing with us, holmes.
冷静 等会就有感觉了
Chill, it'll happen soon.
呦 这他妈是什么
Yo, what the fuck?
老兄 我们不想像那样
Dude. We don't roll like that.
-我擦 这是怎么了 -我操
- What the fuck?! - I'm fucked up.
哦 操
Oh, shit!
太操蛋了
Fuck!
谁想喝点啤酒
Who wants a beer?
混两份离子水 别用水龙头里的
Mix two parts ionized water, do not use tap,
再加一份SEB 千万不要让他见到阳光
and one part SEB. Never leave it in direct sunlight.
用之前摇一摇 千万不要给小孩
Shake well before using, and keep out of reach of children.
我会给你们些眼药滴管 我喜欢你们这群家伙
I'm gonna throw in some eyedroppers because I like you guys.
我会给你看一些好东西 因为我喜欢你们俩个
如果你们办成了这件事 你们会得到丰厚的报酬
You do this thing right, you're looking at a street value
大约100万美金 这是5倍的报酬
right around a hundred grand. That's a 500% return.
-这真是一个完美的交易 -没错
- Which is a beautiful thing. - My man!
街上没人 你们可以走了
The street is clear. You two better bounce.
你做了些什么 Peter
What did you do, Peter?
我只是玩了些惊人的小把戏而已
I just worked the most beautiful little con.
那个女律师会着手调查这个案子的
We're getting the lady lawyer on the case.
我感觉很糟
I feel like shit.
你竟然把他们带到了这里 你到底在想些什么
I can't believe you brought them here. What were you thinking?
实际上 他们中间有个一蠢货
You know, actually, one of those numb-nuts
想改名叫Tony Montana
wants to change his name to Tony Montana.
这他妈的可不是在开玩笑 Peter
This isn't some kind of fucking joke, Peter!
你不可以随便现形
You turned on the wrong moon!
别这样 D 我只是做了我该做的
Come on, D. I did what I had to do.
是啊 但是你知道要付出什么代价吗
Yeah, but at what price?
你根本不清楚这件事能瞬间毁了你
You have no idea how fast this can destroy you.
-你永远不会等到它到来 - 别紧张 好吗
- You'll never see it coming. - Take it easy, OK?
你可能会变成吸血狼人
You could end up a vargulf.
-也行现在就已经太晚了 - 好的 我知道了
- It might already be too late. - OK, I get it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
仅此一次 下不为例
It was a one-time thing.
我只能步行回家 都是因为你
I had to walk home because of you.
你根本不应该为了25元来压榨他们
You couldn't have squeezed them for 25?
吃饭
Eat.
耳蜗和髓鞘
The cochleae and myelin sheaths
的神经部分以及听觉系统
of the neural portion and auditory system
已经得到了提升
are now fully developed.
展示了高度的集中性
Demonstrates extremely high integration.
它正在用铁 氮 磷
The subject is building unique lattice works
来构建一个独特的网状结构
of iron, nitrogen, and phosphorus.
她的前额是否能够
Is the fore portion of the cranium adapting well
扩大她的额前叶
to the enlarging frontal cortex?
很好 她已逐渐具有子宫外受孕的能力
Good. She's rapidly approaching extrauterine viability.
但是我们想减缓形成她这个能力
But we will want to ramp down...
来增加她的寿命
To increase longevity.
我希望能在两周内准备好对她的提取实验
I want her ready for extraction in two weeks.
美极了
It's beautiful.
我把给那个女律师的定金减少了
I dropped the cash off with the lady lawyer.
她说条令上的有些条款可能失效了
She said some of the statutes on the warrants might be expired.
是的 我感觉事情会朝好的方向发展
Yeah, I've got a good feeling about this.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
消防军官依然在继续
Fire marshals are continuing
调查发生在西部仓库的
their investigation into a suspicious fire
这场离奇的大火
at a warehouse in the west end...
报上名来
Announce yourself.
呃 我看见外面的标牌上写着你想要找一个司机
Uh, your sign says you're looking for a driver.
不只是司机 是拖车的司机
Not just a driver, a tow-truck driver.
-我有4级驾照 -是啊 很多人也有
- I've got my class four license. - Yeah, so do a lot of people.
我在找一个视力好 手不抖的人
I'm looking for somebody with a good eye and a steady hand.
这可不是一件容易的事
There's a whole art and a science to it.
鹿角兔
Jackalope.
啊
Ah.
我可不想找些马路杀手来浪费时间
No sense letting perfectly good roadkill go to waste.
不好意思 你是在找
I'm sorry, are you looking for
司机还是找人帮你做填充玩具
a driver or are you looking for an animal stuffer?
一个有能力的人
An operator.
我有两辆车但我只招一个司机
We got two trucks and only one driver.
- 我喜欢那个会飞的猫 - 那是我的小野鸟
- I like the flying cat. - That's my pussy-bird.
你开过拖车吗
You ever drive a hook-'em-up truck before?
嗯 开过几次
Yeah, a couple times.
好吧 你可不能比上个来应聘的人更蠢了
Well, you can't be any worse than the last idiot.
12美元每小时
Pays 12 bucks an hour.
没问题
Works for me.
你需要填一些表格
You'll need to fill out some paperwork.
一个男人和他的孩子
A man and his son were
的尸体在尼克松峡谷的底部被发现
found dead at the bottom of Nickelson Gorge.
警官们认为来自纽约艾伦维尔罗伯特
Authorities believe that Robert Dexter of Ellenville, New York,
和他的儿子死前是沿着一条通往峭壁顶的
and his infant son had been hiking along a footpath
小路上山 最终失足坠落
at the top of the cliff and lost their footing.
嗨
Hey!
死亡原因依旧在调查中
However, the cause of death is still under investigation.
- 喂 我在跟你讲话呢
- Hey! I'm talking to you!
- 你吸毒么 - 什么
- You don't toot the whacky? - What?
我不雇佣吸毒者 无神论者 工党
I don't hire dope fiends, atheists, communists,
娘娘腔 善待动物组织成员和犹太人
nancy boys, PETA whack jobs or Jews.
我知道了
Yeah, got it.
填一下这个
Fill these out.
明天早上六点半来
Be back here tomorrow morning at 6:30.
别迟到了
And, uh, don't be late.
我可以请你喝杯酒吗 你看起来有点孤单
Can I buy you a drink? You look lonely.
我有酒喝
I have a drink...
而且我有人陪
and I have a date.
你可以有酒有人陪 但是你依然会感到孤单
You can have both those things and still be lonely.
嘿 朋友 她是我的
Hey, friend, she's mine.
你听到什么了么 好像有人在抱怨什么
You hear something? Sounded like whining.
是的 是那个男人
Yeah, that's, uh, that's the guy.
我们在约会 他说 朋友 她是我的
That's my date. He said, "Hey, friend, she's mine."
是真的吗 你是他的人
Is that true? You belong to him?
不是
No.
但是
But the thing is,
他脾气有点坏
he's got a little anger management issue.
这个人 这个约会
And this guy, this date,
这个小心眼爱吃醋的脾气又不好的男人
this hypothetical person with the short fuse...
他让你感觉很好么
is he showing you a good time?
一点也不
Not really.
好吧 蠢货
OK, cocksucker...
你最好注意点
You know, you better watch out.
来啊
Come on.
我好想要
I'm so fucking wet.
滚出去
Get out.
你在开玩笑么
Are you fucking kidding me?
- 滚出去 - 你有什么毛病
- Get the fuck out! - What the fuck's your problem?
又是漫长的一天 Godfrey先生
It's been another very long day, Mr. Godfrey.
你可以走了 Lucy马上要来了
You can go. Lucy will be here soon.